{
    "id": "be28a49a9b494bcb8dce24e942b899b7",
    "title": "General English Exercise 2",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "381cdd5ed4cb4f1089e4670dadd717d2",
            "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You don’t know what has happened, ……………………?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do you",
                        "don't you",
                        "did you"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "While passing ………………… the small door, I hurt my head.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "between",
                        "through",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thief was caught …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "green-handed",
                        "blue-handed",
                        "red-handed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If something is ‘All Greek and Latin to you’, you ………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "understand it",
                        "don't understand it",
                        "find it amusing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like to ask …………………… more questions.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The player announced that he ……………………… from the game.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is retiring",
                        "was retiring",
                        "will retire"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Though they were badly outnumbered, the soldiers decided to make a ………………….. effort to conquer the city.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last hole",
                        "last ditch",
                        "last cannon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The students ……………………… when the teacher walked into the room.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stand up",
                        "stood up",
                        "have stood up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They won’t accept this proposal, …………………?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will they",
                        "won't they",
                        "would they"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Will you wait …………………… I return?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "till",
                        "when",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}